If we want to segment our data into even more granular chunks,
إذا أردنا تقسيم بياناتنا إلى أجزاء أكثر دقة،
we can group by multiple columns.
فيمكننا التجميع في أعمدة متعددة.
Imagine yourself as a marketing manager at Parch & Posey,
تخيل أنك مدير تسويق في Posh and Posey،
trying to understand how each account interacted with various advertising channels.
وتحاول فهم كيفية تفاعل كل حساب مع قنوات إعلانية متنوعة.
Which channels are driving traffic and leading to purchases?
ما القنوات التي تقود حركة الزيارات وتؤدي إلى عمليات الشراء؟
Are we investing in channels that aren't worth the cost?
هل نحن نستثمر في قنوات لا تستحق التكلفة؟
How much traffic are we obtaining from each channel?
كم عدد الزيارات التي نحصل عليها من كل قناة؟
One way we might begin to look into these questions,
من الطرق التي قد نبدأ بها النظر في هذه الأسئلة،
is to count up all of the events for each channel,
هي حساب جميع الأحداث لكل قناة،
for each account ID.
لكل معرف حساب.
It looks like the really useful information here is in the events column.
يبدو أن المعلومات المفيدة حقًا هنا في عمود الأحداث.
Let's reorder this to highlight the highest volume channels for each account.
لنعد ترتيب هذا لإبراز أعلى القنوات من حيث الحجم لكل حساب.
You'll notice that account ID comes before events in the order by clause.
ستلاحظ أن معرّف الحساب يأتي قبل الأحداث في عبارة order by.
Here in the results,
هنا في النتائج،
you can see that these are ordered first by account ID,
يمكنك أن ترى هذه مرتبة أولًا حسب معرّف الحساب،
then by events within the account ID.
ثم حسب الأحداث في معرّف الحساب.